<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment_old">Test</string>
    <string name="home_fragment">Home</string>
    <string name="featured_text">Featured Places</string>
    <string name="view_all_text">View All</string>
    <string name="intro_header_text">Celebrity Hang Outs</string>
    <string name="intro_description_text">India is a great country with a haven of tourism delights like wealth of sights, cultural exuberance, and diversity of terrain.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">India speaks for itself as a soul-stirring journey. From its dusty snow trenches, frolic coasts, gripping natural green to the mystic ravines of spirituality and clusters of cultural shades defining the raw beauty, India captures the heart of every tourist. Discover the different facets of this multicolored country as it shapes your vision at every of its fold. With the countrys tourism branched into several forms, India has a chunk for every kind of a traveler.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_header_text">More Information</string>
    <string name="home_text">Incredible India</string>
    <string name="dine_text">Lets go and have Delicious Food</string>
    <string name="shop_text">Shop with Style</string>
    <string name="historic_text">Historical places</string>
    <string name="nightlife_text">Celebarte the life at night</string>
    <string name="dine_fragment">Dining</string>
    <string name="shop_fragment">Shopping</string>
    <string name="historic_fragment">Historic</string>
    <string name="Historic_alternative">Historic Places</string>
    <string name="nightlife_fragment">Nightlife</string>
    <string name="nightlife_alternative">Bars, Lounges &amp; Dance Clubs</string>
    <string name="image_content_description">Image of Attraction</string>
    <string name="tab_image_content_description">Category Image</string>
    <string name="subtitle_prefix_detail_screen">Celebrity </string>
    <string name="like_button_content_description">Like Button</string>
    <string name="phone_prefix"><b>Phone: </b></string>
    <string name="website_prefix"><b>Website: </b></string>
    <string name="url_prefix">http://</string>
    <string name="more_info_link">View More Info</string>
    <string name="less_info_link">View Less Info</string>
    <string name="share_info">Share this Attraction with&#8230;</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Reset Favorites</string>
    <string name="action_about">About App</string>
    <string name="fav_saved">Saved</string>
    <string name="fav_save">Save</string>
    <string name="call_icon">Call</string>
    <string name="share_icon">Share</string>
    <string name="web_icon">Web</string>
    <string name="map_icon">Map</string>
    <string name="like_icon">Save</string>
    <string name="detail_blurb_header">About</string>
    <string name="detail_descrip_header">More Info</string>
    <string name="attr_name_short_example">Aish</string>
    <string name="attr_name_long_example">Arpora Saturday Night Bazaar</string>
    <string name="attr_address_multiline_example">Somajiguda Lobby Level, The Park Opp Raily Station,     Necklace Rd, Somajiguda, Hyderabad, Telangana 500082</string>
    <string name="attr_address_single_line_example">Somajiguda Lobby Level, Necklace Rd, Somajiguda, Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="attr_phone_example">(404) 262&#45;2675</string>
    <string name="attr_description_example">Courtly Andhran restaurant with royal     Nizam decor within a stylish high-end hotel.</string>
    <string name="attr_detail_description_example">An ideal space to create unforgettable memories, The Park hotels\' signature style blends sophistication with local art and culture to create international chic. Redefining luxury, The Park\'s five star hotels in ten of India's most vibrant cities invite you to stay inspired.</string>
    <string name="attr_detail_blurb_example">Now it\'s time to celebrate our legacy of great service and fun, and we invite you to join in for our year long festivities.</string>
    <string name="three_dots">...</string>

    <string-array name="attr_name">
        <item>AISH</item>
        <item>AGASHIYE</item>
        <item>BHARAWAN DA DHABA</item>
        <item>HOTEL SARAVANA BHAVAN</item>
        <item>Tito’s Club</item>
        <item>Deltin Royale Casino</item>
        <item>Shroom Nightclub</item>
        <item>The Blue Frog</item>
        <item>Arpora Saturday Night Bazaar</item>
        <item>Fashion Street</item>
        <item>Colaba Causeway</item>
        <item>Sarojini</item>
        <item>Taj Mahal</item>
        <item>Qutub Minar</item>
        <item>Hawa Mahal</item>
        <item>Charminar</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_category">
        <item>Dining</item>
        <item>Dining</item>
        <item>Dining</item>
        <item>Dining</item>
        <item>Nightlife</item>
        <item>Nightlife</item>
        <item>Nightlife</item>
        <item>Nightlife</item>
        <item>Nightlife</item>
        <item>Shopping</item>
        <item>Shopping</item>
        <item>Shopping</item>
        <item>Historic</item>
        <item>Historic</item>
        <item>Historic</item>
        <item>Historic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_address_multi">
        <item>Somajiguda Lobby Level, The Park Opp Raily Station,, Necklace Rd, Somajiguda, Hyderabad, Telangana 500082</item>
        <item>Bhadra Road, Opp. Sidi Saiyad Jali, Lal Darwaja, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380001</item>
        <item>Near Town Hall, Amritsar, Punjab 143001</item>
        <item>21, Kenneth Ln, Egmore, Chennai, Tamil Nadu 600008</item>
        <item>Titos Ln, Saunta Vaddo, Goa, 403516</item>
        <item>Noah's Ark, RND Jetty, Dayanand Bandodkar Road, Panaji, Goa 403001</item>
        <item>Third Floor, The Crescent Mall, Lado Sarai, Mehrauli, New Delhi, Delhi 110030</item>
        <item>No. 3, MSR West Park, Church Street, Ashok Nagar, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560001</item>
        <item>Arpora, Goa 403519</item>
        <item>Mahatma Gandhi Road, Marine Lines, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400020</item>
        <item>Bakery Ln, Army Area, Nofra, Navy Nagar, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400005</item>
        <item>Sarojini Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110023</item>
        <item>Dharmapuri, Forest Colony, Tajganj, Agra, Uttar Pradesh 282001</item>
        <item>Mehrauli, New Delhi, Delhi 110030</item>
        <item>Hawa Mahal Rd, Badi Choupad, J.D.A. Market, Kanwar Nagar, Jaipur, Rajasthan 302002</item>
        <item>Char Kaman, Ghansi Bazaar, Hyderabad, Telangana 500002</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_address">
        <item>Somajiguda Lobby Level, The Park Opp Raily Station, Necklace Rd, Somajiguda, Hyderabad, Telangana</item>
        <item>Bhadra Road, Opp. Sidi Saiyad Jali, Lal Darwaja, Ahmedabad, Gujarat</item>
        <item>Near Town Hall, Amritsar, Punjab</item>
        <item>21, Kenneth Ln, Egmore, Chennai, Tamil Nadu</item>
        <item>Titos Ln, Saunta Vaddo, Goa</item>
        <item>Noah's Ark, RND Jetty, Dayanand Bandodkar Road, Panaji, Goa</item>
        <item>Third Floor, The Crescent Mall, Lado Sarai, Mehrauli, New Delhi, Delhi</item>
        <item>No. 3, MSR West Park, Church Street, Ashok Nagar, Bengaluru, Karnataka</item>
        <item>Arpora, Goa</item>
        <item>Mahatma Gandhi Road, Marine Lines, Mumbai, Maharashtra</item>
        <item>Bakery Ln, Army Area, Nofra, Navy Nagar, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra</item>
        <item>Sarojini Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi</item>
        <item>Dharmapuri, Forest Colony, Tajganj, Agra, Uttar Pradesh</item>
        <item>Mehrauli, New Delhi, Delhi</item>
        <item>Hawa Mahal Rd, Badi Choupad, J.D.A. Market, Kanwar Nagar, Jaipur, Rajasthan</item>
        <item>Char Kaman, Ghansi Bazaar, Hyderabad, Telangana</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_coordinates">
        <item>geo:0,0?q=17.4236,78.4620(The Park)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=23.0270,72.5815(Agashiye)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=31.6259,74.8777(Bharawan Da Dhaba)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=23.0270,72.5815(Saravana bhavan)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=15.5563,73.7532(Tito’s club)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=15.5006,73.8313(Deltin royale casino)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=28.5246,77.1908(Shroom nightclub)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=12.9744,77.6068(Blue frog)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=15.5768,73.7617(arpora)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=18.9389,72.8301(fashion street)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=18.9172,72.8286(Colaba Causeway Market)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=28.5773,77.1963(Sarojini)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=27.1750,78.0422(Taj Mahal)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=28.5244,77.1855(Qutb Minar)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=26.9239,75.8267(Hawa Mahal)</item>
        <item>geo:0,0?q=17.3616,78.4747(Charminar)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_phone">
        <item>040-23456789</item>
        <item>079-25506946</item>
        <item>183-2532575</item>
        <item>044-28192055</item>
        <item>9822765002</item>
        <item>9819698196</item>
        <item>9624054444</item>
        <item>7411099549</item>
        <item>09922100001</item>
        <item>09647484838</item>
        <item>08234575556</item>
        <item>07464849475</item>
        <item>09277768876</item>
        <item>08567677767</item>
        <item>09454565556</item>
        <item>09756776769</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_phone_link">
        <item>tel:04023456789</item>
        <item>tel:07925506946</item>
        <item>tel:1832532575</item>
        <item>tel:04428192055</item>
        <item>tel:09822765002</item>
        <item>tel:09819698196</item>
        <item>tel:09624054444</item>
        <item>tel:07411099549</item>
        <item>tel:09922100001</item>
        <item>tel:09647484838</item>
        <item>tel:08234575556</item>
        <item>tel:07464849475</item>
        <item>tel:09277768876</item>
        <item>tel:08567677767</item>
        <item>tel:09454565556</item>
        <item>tel:09756776769</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_website">
        <item>www.theparkhotels.com/hyderabad.html</item>
        <item>www.houseofmg.com</item>
        <item>www.tripadvisor.in/Restaurant_Review-g303884-d2322746-Reviews-Bharawan_Da_Dhaba-Amritsar_Amritsar_District_Punjab.html</item>
        <item>www.saravanabhavan.com/</item>
        <item>titosgoa.com/</item>
        <item>www.deltin.com</item>
        <item>shroom.co.in</item>
        <item>bengalurubluefrog.club</item>
        <item>www.snmgoa.com</item>
        <item>www.tripadvisor.in/Attraction_Review-g304554-d2443565-Reviews-Fashion_Street-Mumbai_Maharashtra.html</item>
        <item>www.tripadvisor.in/Attraction_Review-g304554-d6570937-Reviews-Colaba_Causeway_Market-Mumbai_Maharashtra.html</item>
        <item>www.justdial.com/Delhi/Paul-Shoes-Main-Market-Sarojini-Nagar-Market/011PXX11-XX11-001018446943-X2K3_BZDET</item>
        <item>www.tajmahal.gov.in/</item>
        <item>www.delhitourism.gov.in/delhitourism/tourist_place/qutab_minar.jsp</item>
        <item>en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawa_Mahal</item>
        <item>www.telanganatourism.gov.in/partials/destinations/heritage-spots/hyderabad/charminar.html</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_description">
        <item>Courtly Andhran restaurant with royal Nizam decor within a stylish high-end hotel.</item>
        <item>Terrace restaurant at a 1920s hotel serving traditional Gujarati dishes and thalis.</item>
        <item>Best punjabi food</item>
        <item>Long-running international chain serving up South Indian vegetarian dishes, including dosas.</item>
        <item>Typical nightspot offering a variety of cocktails and beer, plus DJ music and dancing.</item>
        <item>Lively offshore casino offering numerous games and tournaments, live entertainment and dining.</item>
        <item>State-of-the-art nightclub known for top DJs and out-of-the-ordinary, edible cocktails.</item>
        <item>State-of-the-art nightspot with a regular line-up of DJs hosting party evenings and a global menu</item>
        <item>Energetic open-air night market known for its array of goods and food stalls, plus cocktails and DJs.</item>
        <item>Fashion Street refers to a cluster of over 385 street side clothing shops on MG Road near Azad Maidan and is opposite to Bombay Gymkhana, in South Mumbai, India. The market is located just opposite VSNL office building at Mahatma Gandhi Road</item>
        <item>Colaba Causeway, a street side shopping destination of South ... Causeway market is heaven for book readers, find almost any book of any author you like.</item>
        <item>At the Sarojini Nagar Market you get fashionable clothes at affordable prices.</item>
        <item>The Taj Mahal is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the south bank of the Yamuna river in the Indian city of Agra. It was commissioned in 1632 by the Mughal emperor, Shah Jahan, to house the tomb of his favourite wife, Mumtaz Mahal.</item>
        <item>The Qutub Minar, also spelled as Qutab Minar, or Qutb Minar, is the tallest minaret in the world made up of bricks. The minaret forms a part of the Qutab complex, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Mehrauli area of Delhi, India</item>
        <item>The Hawa Mahal is within walking distance of City Palace and Jantar Mantar.</item>
        <item>There is an unknown underground tunnel that Qutb Shah has said to have made as an escape route, which connected the Golconda Fort to the Charminar</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attr_blurb">
        <item>Now its time to celebrate our legacy of great service and fun, and we invite you to join in for our year long festivities.</item>
        <item>Agashiye’ in Gujarati means on the terrace. This stunning Gujarati Thali restaurant is spread over two huge terraces interconnected by a smaller one that houses a wooden cottage. Agashiye is an iconic restaurant in Ahmedabad. It celebrates Gujarati food, the most varied vegetarian cuisine in India. Agashiye is ranked as one of the top restaurants in Ahmedabad by Zomato, India’s leading restaurant search and discovery service and as one of the ‘ten best restaurants in India’ by both Trip Advisor and NDTV. Your visit to Ahmedabad is incomplete without experiencing a Gujarati meal here.</item>
        <item>Explore delicious dishes at Bharawan Da Dhaba in Amritsar.</item>
        <item>Success begets success. When the efforts are sincere, intention noble and the aspiration high, success is a natural byproduct. However, we don't believe in resting on our laurels. We have always reinvented ourselves in our unswerving endeavor to offer unrivalled quality and taste.</item>
        <item>Enjoy partying in the best night clubs in Goa and have a blast with your friend circle clubbing with music and alcohol @ Titos night clubs, Baga.</item>
        <item>Featuring India's largest casinos and integrated resorts in carefully chosen locations, Deltin Royale has redefined the country's gaming and hospitality services.</item>
        <item>The Nightclub is an alternate world of sensory perceptions with state of the art audio systems and cutting-edge visual projection technology. A true evolution of the clubbing experience, Shroom has changed India’s nightscape with edible cocktails, fluid dishes and form-free sound. Awarded The Best Nightclub / Discotheque of 2012 by Times Food and Nightlife.</item>
        <item>blueFROG Bangalore is a state-of-the-art club spread over 10,000 square feet with floor-to-ceiling glass walls. The acoustically treated timber panelling and futuristic sound controlled lighting ensure that you have the ultimate music experience.</item>
        <item>Shopping at the Saturday Night Bazaar at Arpora is a great weekend activity, as the market offers an exciting mix of shopping opportunities ranging from sumptuous foodstuff, herbs and spices to handicrafts, bags, accessories, designer jewellery, rugs and carpets. The “night” factor of the Arpora market not only allows you to shop while the weather is pleasant but also adds a happening feel to it.</item>
        <item>The market is located just opposite VSNL office building at Mahatma Gandhi Road.</item>
        <item>These days, Mumbai is known more for its designer shops and malls than its ... The everyday carnival that is the Colaba Causeway market</item>
        <item>Sarojini Nagar is a place that is situated in the south west District of Delhi state in India. </item>
        <item>The Taj Mahal complex includes a large garden, a reflecting pool, a mosque and other mausoleums.</item>
        <item>There are numerous inscriptions on the Qutub Minar in Arabic and Nagari characters.</item>
        <item>Hawa Mahal is a palace in Jaipur, India. It is constructed of red and pink sandstone. The palace sits on the edge of the City Palace, Jaipur, and extends to the zenana, or women's chambers.</item>
        <item>The Charminar, constructed in 1591, is a monument and mosque located in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The landmark has become a global icon of Hyderabad, listed among the most recognized structures of India</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
